Liam D Hall

Experienced in graphics design in clothing manufacturing as well as direct sales and working in a customer-facing role in estate agency, leisure and licensed premises industries. Completed the Code Institute's Full Stack Software Development course. Holds a full UK driving licence and owns a car.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Software Development Diploma — Code Institute

Jun 2021

Achieved Grade: Distinction

• View all my projects at: liam-hall.herokuapp.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Graphics Designer — Rock The Dragon

Mar 2020 - Present

- Manually tested the new company website relaying the issues I found to the company hired to build it.
- Designed and created over 50 logos for dance schools across the UK.
- Identified bottlenecks in the order processing workflow and created and implemented a production system/strategy that increased production by 100% (from 20-25 orders a day to 40-50). My system was more efficient, reducing bottlenecking of certain steps and simplified many processes so people with little training could step into many roles.
- Gained an understanding of designing whilst having to consider limitations imposed when using physical media.
- Archived professional proficiency in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Hotfix Era.

Manager — Cinnabar

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

- Lead teams of up to 7 people for 11-hour shifts making sure everyone maintained focus and morale.
- Exceeded sale targets each month by introducing incentives and rewards for bartenders that achieved and surpassed their personal target at weekends, as well as introducing new events / special deals for each weekday which resulted in an increased number of customers during the week.

Cocktail Bartender — CBK, Rotorua, New Zealand May 2018 – May 2019

Cocktail Bartender — Scotty's, St Anton, Austria Dec 2017 – Apr 2018

Supervisor — Cinnabar Sep 2015 – Dec 2017

Cocktail Bartender — The Snug Mar 2015 – Sep 2015

Operations Manager — Solutions For Property Aug 2014 – Mar 2015

 Ran all of the logistics for the plumbing and maintenance services such as time, access, approval of all jobs and placing them on the system tracker to inform the engineers and workmen Phone: +44 (0) 7367 583649

Email: hall.d.liam@gmail.com

Portfolio: liam-hall.herokuapp.com

Github: github.com/LiamDHall

SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 including Grids and Flexbox

Libraries & Frameworks

Django, Flask, jQuery, Bootstrap

Databases

MongoDB, AWS S3, NoSQL, SQL

Tools & Platforms

Git, GitHub, Heroku, Balsamiq Wireframing

Software

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Mircosoft Office 365, Cutting Master Pro 4,

INTERESTS

Snowboarding, Krav Maga, Digital Art in Photoshop, Baking, Roller Skating.